Guide to the New-York Historical Society Portrait Collection, circa 1640-2020 (bulk, 1800-1950) PR 52
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Individuals and Family Groups
  - Subseries I.A. Individuals and Family Groups: Small Format
    - Van Nest (Offsite-box 141)
    - Van Rensselaer (Offsite-box 141)
    - Van Rensselaer, Stephen (Offsite-box 141)
    - Van Santvoord, Alfred (Offsite-box 141)
    - Van Wyck (Offsite-box 141)
    - Varick, Richard (Offsite-box 141)
    - Vassar (Offsite-box 141)
    - Vere, Francis (Offsite-box 141)
    - Vernon, Edward (Offsite-box 141)
    - Vespucci, Amerigo (Offsite-box 141)
    - Viele, Egbert L. (Offsite-box 141)
    - Vincent (Offsite-box 141)
    - Vinton (Offsite-box 141)
    - Voltaire (Offsite-box 141)
    - Voorhees (Offsite-box 141)
    - Wa-Wz (29 folders) (Offsite-box 142)
    - Wade (Offsite-box 145)
    - Wadsworth, James S. (Offsite-box 145)
    - Wagner (Offsite-box 145)
    - Wagner, Robert F. (Offsite-box 145)
    - Wainwright (Offsite-box 145)
    - Waite, Morrison R. (Offsite-box 145)
    - Walker (Offsite-box 145)
    - Wall (Offsite-box 145)
    - Wall, Alexander J., and wife (Offsite-box 145)
    - Wallace (Offsite-box 145)
    - Wallace, Lewis (Offsite-box 145)
    - Walter (Offsite-box 145)
    - Walton (Offsite-box 145)
    - Ward (2 folders) (Offsite-box 146)
    - Ward, John Quincy Adams (Offsite-box 146)
    - Warner (Offsite-box 146)
    - Warner, Maria Sarah (Offsite-box 146)
    - Warren (Offsite-box 146)
    - Warren, John Borlase (Offsite-box 146)
    - Warren, Joseph (Offsite-box 146)
    - Warren, Peter (Offsite-box 146)
    - Washburn (Offsite-box 146)
    - Washburne, Elihu B. (Offsite-box 146)
    - Washington (Offsite-box 147)
    - Washington, George (Offsite-box 147)
      ....Individual portraits by:
      ........Chappel, A.
      ........Du Simetiere
      ........Peale Family
      ........Savage, Edward
      ........Sharpless
      ........Stuart, Gilbert (4 folders)
      ........Trumball, John
      ........Wright, Joseph and Patience
    - Washington, George (continued) (Offsite-box 148)
      Portraits (continued)
      ........Miscellaneous Artists
      ........Unidentified Artists
      ....Allegorical portraits
      ....Silhouettes (1 from George Settlemeyer, 1959)
      ....Bicentennial Portraits
      ....Family Portraits
      Scenes From His Life
      ....Prior to the Revolution
      ....During the Revolution (2 folders)
      ....Inauguration and Presidency (for more see Subject File--FF--Wars--Events)
      Associated Buildings
      ....Mount Vernon
      ....Family Houses
      ....Headquarters
    - Washington, George (continued) (Offsite-box 149)
      Sculpture and Monuments
      Associated Furniture and Ceramics
    - Washington, George (continued) (Box 149.1)
      Portrait of Washington in an oval, gilt frame surmounted by an eagle.
    - Washington, Martha (Offsite-box 149)
      One item the gift of George Settlemeyer, 1959.
    - Washington, Mary Ball (Offsite-box 149)
    - Watson (Offsite-box 149)
    - Watt, James (Offsite-box 149)
    - Watts (Offsite-box 150)
    - Watts, John (Offsite-box 150)
    - Wayne, Anthony (Offsite-box 150)
    - Webb (2 folders) (Offsite-box 150)
    - Webb, Alexander S. (Offsite-box 150)
    - Webb, G. Creighton (Offsite-box 150)
    - Webb, James Watson, and family (Offsite-box 150)
    - Webb, Lila Osgood (Offsite-box 150)
    - Webster (Offsite-box 150)
    - Webster, Daniel (2 folders) (Offsite-box 150)
    - Webster, Noah (Offsite-box 151)
    - Weed, Thurlow (Offsite-box 151)
    - Weitzel, Godfrey (Offsite-box 151)
    - Welch (Offsite-box 151)
    - Welles, Gideon (Offsite-box 151)
    - Wellington, Arthur Wellesley (Offsite-box 151)
    - Wells (Offsite-box 151)
    - Wendover (Offsite-box 151)
    - Wentworth, John (Offsite-box 151)
    - Wesley, John (Offsite-box 151)
    - West (Offsite-box 151)
    - West, Benjamin (Offsite-box 151)
    - Wheaton (Offsite-box 151)
    - Wheeler (Offsite-box 151)
    - Wheeler, William A. (Offsite-box 151)
    - White, A-Z (Offsite-box 151)
      Among many others: Moses and Mrs. White from George Settlemeyer, 1959.
    - White, William (Offsite-box 151)
    - Whitman, Walt (3 folders) (Offsite-box 152)
    - Whitney (Offsite-box 152)
    - Whittier, John Greenleaf (Offsite-box 152)
    - Wilde (Offsite-box 152)
    - Wilkes, Charles (Offsite-box 152)
    - Wilkes, John (Offsite-box 152)
    - Wilkinson (Offsite-box 152)
    - Willard (Offsite-box 152)
    - Willcox (Offsite-box 152)
    - Willett, Morinus (Offsite-box 152)
    - Williams (2 folders) (Offsite-box 152)
    - Williams, Jonathan (Offsite-box 152)
    - Williams, Leighton, and family (Offsite-box 152)
    - Williams, Otho H. (Offsite-box 153)
    - Williams, William (Offsite-box 153)
    - Williamson, Hugh (Offsite-box 153)
    - Willis (Offsite-box 153)
    - Willis, Nathaniel P. (Offsite-box 153)
    - Wilson (2 folders) (Offsite-box 153)
    - Wilson, Henry (Offsite-box 153)
    - Wilson, Woodrow (2 folders) (Offsite-box 153)
    - Winslow, John A. (Offsite-box 154)
    - Winston, Lillian (Offsite-box 154)
    - Winthrop (Offsite-box 154)
    - Winthrop, John (Offsite-box 154)
    - Winthrop, Theodore (Offsite-box 154)
    - Wirt, William (Offsite-box 154)
    - Wise, Henry A. (Offsite-box 154)
    - Wistar, Caspar (Offsite-box 154)
    - Withers (Offsite-box 154)
    - Withers, George (Offsite-box 154)
    - Wolcott, Oliver (Offsite-box 154)
    - Wolfe, James (Offsite-box 154)
    - Wood (2 folders) (Offsite-box 154)
    - Wood, Benjamin (Offsite-box 154)
    - Wood, Fernando (Offsite-box 154)
    - Woodbury, Levi (Offsite-box 155)
    - Woodhull (Offsite-box 155)
    - Woodman (Offsite-box 155)
    - Woodruff (Offsite-box 155)
    - Woods (Offsite-box 155)
    - Woodward (Offsite-box 155)
    - Wool, John E. (Offsite-box 155)
    - Woolsey (Offsite-box 155)
    - Wooster, David (Offsite-box 155)
    - Worden, John L. (Offsite-box 155)
    - Worth, W. J. (Offsite-box 155)
    - Wright (2 folders) (Offsite-box 155)
    - Wright, Silas (Offsite-box 155)
    - Wyman (Offsite-box 155)
    - Y miscellaneous (2 folders) (Offsite-box 156)
    - Yates (Offsite-box 156)
    - Yates, Richard (Offsite-box 156)
    - Young (Offsite-box 156)
    - Young, Brigham, and family (Offsite-box 156)
    - Z miscellaneous (Offsite-box 156)
    - Zabriskie, George A., and family (Offsite-box 156)
    - Zagonyi, Charles D. (Offsite-box 156)
  - Subseries I.B. Individuals and Family Groups: Medium Format
    Each sitter is filed alphabetically and identified. Sitters or surnames comprising their own folder are so identified.
    - Abber, Colly (Drawer Medium)
    - Abeel (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Abeel, Catherine Emeline
      Abeel, John Howard
      Abeel, John Neilson
      Abeel, Magdalen
    - Ackland, Harriet (Drawer Medium)
    - Adams, Charles Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - Adams, Frederick B., Jr. (Drawer Medium)
    - Adams, John (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Adams, John Quincy (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Adams, Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Adams, Samuel Gardner CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Adams, William [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Adelman, Joseph and Bertha (Drawer Medium)
    - Adet, Pierre Auguste (Drawer Medium)
    - Agassiz, Louis (Drawer Medium)
    - Agnew, Alexander McL. (Drawer Medium)
    - Agnew, J. Holmes (Drawer Medium)
    - Agnus, Felix (Drawer Medium)
    - Albery, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Albright, Harriet Langdon (gravestone) (Drawer Medium)
    - Alden, Henry H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Alden, Roger (Drawer Medium)
    - Alexander, E. P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Alexander, James D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Alexander, James W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Alexander, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Alger, Russell A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Allen, Henry T. (Drawer Medium)
    - Allen, Richard (Drawer Medium)
    - Allen, Stephen (Drawer Medium)
    - Alphane, Walter C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Altemus, James A. and Rosalie (Drawer Medium)
    - Amherst, Jeffrey (Drawer Medium)
    - Ampudia (Drawer Medium)
    - Amundsen, Roald (Drawer Medium)
    - Anderson, Alexander (Drawer Medium)
    - Anderson, C. V. (Drawer Medium)
    - Anderson, George Burgwyn (Drawer Medium)
    - Anderson, Robert (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Anderson, Robert H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Anderson, S. R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Andre, John (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Anthony, Jesse B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Applegate, Abram W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Appleton, William H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Apthorp, Charles Ward and wife (Drawer Medium)
    - Arago, Francois (Drawer Medium)
    - Aranda, Count (Drawer Medium)
    - Argyll, John Douglas Sutherland Campbell, duke of (Drawer Medium)
    - Armstrong, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Armstrong, Frank C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Armstrong, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Arnold, Benedict (Drawer Medium)
    - Arta, Regine (Drawer Medium)
    - Arthur, Chester A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Ashburton, Alexander Baring (Lord Ashburton) (Drawer Medium)
    - Aspinwall, William Henry [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Astor, John Jacob III (Drawer Medium)
    - Astor, Caroline Schermerhorn (Drawer Medium)
    - Auchmuty, Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Audubon, John James (Drawer Medium)
    - Avery, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Axtel, Daniel (Drawer Medium)
    - Ayers, Romeyn B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Ayme, Henri (Drawer Medium)
    - Ayme, Sophie, Carlton, and Eugenie (Drawer Medium)
    - Babcock, Samuel D. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Babcock, W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bache, Theophylact (Drawer Medium)
    - Bacon, Henry D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bacon, Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Bacon, Robert L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Baden-Powell, Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Badger, George E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bagley, Worth (Drawer Medium)
    - Bagoe, George T., and children (Drawer Medium)
    - Bailey, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Bailey, Theodorus (Drawer Medium)
    - Baird, Spencer F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Baker, Edward D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Baker, George F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Baker, Josephine (Drawer Medium)
    - Baker, Newton D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Baker, William B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Balboa, Vasco Nunez de (Drawer Medium)
    - Balch, Charles Leland CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Baldwin, Albert Henry (Drawer Medium)
    - Baldwin, Elihu Whittlesey (Drawer Medium)
    - Baldwin, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Baldwin, Henry (Drawer Medium)
    - Balestier, Charles Wolcott (Drawer Medium)
    - Balfe, M. W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Baltzell, Charles and relations (Drawer Medium)
    - Bancroft, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Banker, Ed (Drawer Medium)
    - Banks, Henry W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Banks, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Banks, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Banks, Nathaniel P. (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Barbour, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Barbour, Philip Pendleton (Drawer Medium)
    - Bard, Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Barker, Jacob (Drawer Medium)
    - Barker, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Barlow, Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - Barlow, Joel (Drawer Medium)
    - Barnard, J. G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Barnes, Albert (Drawer Medium)
    - Barnes, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Barnes, John Sanford (Drawer Medium)
    - Barnum, P. T. (Phineas Taylor) and family (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Barre, Isaac (Drawer Medium)
    - Barry, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Barry, Thomas H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Barry, William T. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bartholomew, J. G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bartlett, Josiah (Drawer Medium)
    - Bartlett, John Russell (Drawer Medium)
    - Bartolomeo Veneto (Drawer Medium)
    - Barye, Antoine Louis (Drawer Medium)
    - Bascom, Henry Bidleman (Drawer Medium)
    - Bayard, Anne Stuyvesant (Drawer Medium)
    - Bayard, Elise Justine (Drawer Medium)
    - Bayard, George Dashiell (Drawer Medium)
    - Bayard, Lazare (Drawer Medium)
    - Bayard, Lazare, Mrs. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bayard, Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Bayard, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Bayne, Daniel K. (Drawer Medium)
    - Beach (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Beach, Alfred Ely
      Beach, Moses Sperry
      Beach, Moses Yale
    - Beaconfield, Lord (Drawer Medium)
    - Beaujeu (Drawer Medium)
    - Beauregard, G. T. (Drawer Medium)
    - Beardsley, Mr. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Becker, Dr. (Drawer Medium)
    - Beckwith, James Carroll (Drawer Medium)
    - Beckwith, James Carroll, Mrs. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bedell, Gregory T. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bee, Barnard Elliott (Drawer Medium)
    - Beebe, Will (Drawer Medium)
    - Beecher, Henry Ward and family (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Beecher, Lyman (Drawer Medium)
    - Beechey, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Beekman (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Beekman, Abraham
      Beekman, Cornelia
      Beekman, Gerard (1653-1723)
      Beekman, Gerard (1774-1833)
      Beekman, Henry Rutgers
      Beekman, James Hyde (separate folder)
      Beekman, James William (separate folder)
      Beekman, J. W., Mrs.
      Beekman, Josephine (or Mary Elizabeth?)
      Beekman, Magdalen Abeel
      Beekman, William (1684-1770)
      Beekman, William (1725-1795)
    - Beinert, Clarence (Drawer Medium)
    - Belancourt, Richard (Drawer Medium)
    - Bell, Clark (Drawer Medium)
    - Bell, Jonathan (Drawer Medium)
    - Bell, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Belknap, Jeremy (Drawer Medium)
    - Belknap, William W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bellini, Giovanni (Drawer Medium)
    - Bellows, H. W. [can't find 4/09] (Drawer Medium)
    - Beluche, Renato (Drawer Medium)
    - Bendigo, William Thompson (Drawer Medium)
    - Benedict, E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Benham, Henry William (Drawer Medium)
    - Benien (of Georgia) (Drawer Medium)
    - Benjamin, Judah P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Benjamin, Samuel N. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bentley, Uriah (Drawer Medium)
    - Benton, Egbert (Drawer Medium)
    - Benton, Thomas H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Benton, Thomas H., Jr. (Drawer Medium)
    - Benton, William P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Berdan, H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bergh, Henry (Drawer Medium)
    - Berghem, Nicholas (Drawer Medium)
    - Berkeley, Norborne (Baron de Bottetourt) (Drawer Medium)
    - Bernheimer, Charles Leopold (Drawer Medium)
      The Bernheimer photo was returned to the Charles Bernheimer papers (MS 58) from which it had been separated. June 2019.
    - Berrian, John Macpherson (Drawer Medium)
    - Berry, H. G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Besant, Walter (Drawer Medium)
    - Bethune, G. W., Mrs. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bethune, George W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Betts, W. R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bibb, Henry (Drawer Medium)
    - Bibby, Mrs. John (Drawer Medium)
    - Bibby, Justine V. D. H. (Mrs. William Fisher) (Drawer Medium)
    - Bibby, S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Biddle, G. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Biddle, Nicholas (Drawer Medium)
    - Bidwell, W. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bienville, Jean Baptiste Le Moyne, sieur de (Drawer Medium)
    - Bigg, William Redmore (Drawer Medium)
    - Bingham, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Birch, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Birney, David (Drawer Medium)
    - Birney, James G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bishop, William Avery (Drawer Medium)
    - Bispham, David (Drawer Medium)
    - Black, George Alexander CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Black, L. S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Black, John C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Blaine, James Gillespie (Drawer Medium)
    - Blair, Austin (Drawer Medium)
    - Blair, Francis (Frank) Preston, Jr. (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Blair, John, Jr. (Drawer Medium)
    - Blake, Homer Crane (Drawer Medium)
    - Blake, Lillie Devereux (Drawer Medium)
    - Blakely, Mathew James (Drawer Medium)
    - Blatchford, Samuel [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Blease, Cole L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bleckley, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Bleecker, Anthony (Drawer Medium)
    - Blenker, Louis (Drawer Medium)
    - Bliss (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Bliss, Cornelius N.
      Bliss, George Theodore
      Bliss, George Theodore, Mrs.
      Bliss, George Theodore, Mrs., with Susan Dwight Bliss
      Bliss, Tasker H.
    - Bloomer, Amelia Jenks (Drawer Medium)
    - Bloomfield, Smith CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Blucher, Prince (Drawer Medium)
    - Blunt, James G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bly, Nellie (Drawer Medium)
    - Bocciardi, Clemente (Drawer Medium)
    - Boel, Henricus (Drawer Medium)
    - Bogardus, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Boggs, C. S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bolivar, Simon (Drawer Medium)
    - Bolton, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Bonacum, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Bonci, Alessandro (Drawer Medium)
    - Bonheur, Rosa (Drawer Medium)
    - Bonington, Richard Parkes (Drawer Medium)
    - Bonnat, Leon (Drawer Medium)
    - Bonnet, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Booth, Evangeline Cory (Drawer Medium)
    - Booth, H. A. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Booth, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Bostwick, Isaac (Drawer Medium)
    - Botta, Carlo (Drawer Medium)
    - Boucher, Francois (Drawer Medium)
    - Boucher, Jonathan (Drawer Medium)
    - Boudinot, Elias (Drawer Medium)
    - Boughton (Drawer Medium)
    - Bouguereau, William-Adolphe (Drawer Medium)
    - Bourne, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Bowen, George Washington (Drawer Medium)
    - Bowen, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Bowen, John McE. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bowen, John S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bowen, Thomas M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Boyd, Linn (Drawer Medium)
    - Boydell, Alderman (Drawer Medium)
    - Boyle, Jeremiah Tilford (Drawer Medium)
    - Braddock, Edward (Drawer Medium)
    - Bradford, Thomas (1745-1838) (Drawer Medium)
    - Bradford, Thomas (1781-1851) (Drawer Medium)
    - Bradford, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Bradhurst, Mary Smith (Drawer Medium)
    - Bradish, Luther (Drawer Medium)
    - Bradley, Edward Augustus CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Bradley, Joseph P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bragg, Edward L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Brain, Daniel L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Brainerd, C. N. (family group) (Drawer Medium)
    - Branch, L. O'Bryan (Drawer Medium)
    - Bratton, Sam Gilbert (Drawer Medium)
    - Braxton, Carter (Drawer Medium)
    - Breck, Samuel G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Breckenridge, John C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Breckinridge, Robert J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Brent, T. L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Brewer, David Josiah (Drawer Medium)
    - Bricker, John W. (John William) (Drawer Medium)
    - Bridgeman, Oliver (Drawer Medium)
    - Briggs, Herman M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Brion, Luis (Drawer Medium)
    - Brisacier, Guillaume, de (Drawer Medium)
    - Broad, J. Astor (Drawer Medium)
    - Bronner, Leonard Jr. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bronson, Isaac (Drawer Medium)
    - Brooke, John M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Brooke, John R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Brooke, Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Brookes, Alfred (family group) (Drawer Medium)
    - Brooks (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Brooks, Mrs.
      Brooks, Erastus
      Brooks, Frank L.
      Brooks, James
      Brooks, John
      Brooks, Phillips
    - Brougham, Lord (Drawer Medium)
    - Brown (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Brown, Aaron V.
      Brown, David Paul
      Brown, H. K.
      Brown, Henry B.
      Brown, Hiram L.
      Brown, Hugh Stowell
      Brown, Jacob
      Brown, James M. [crossed out]
      Brown, John (separate folder)
      Brown, John C.
      Brown, Milton
      Brown, Morris
      Brown, Nicholas
      Brown, Preston
      Brown, William Wells
    - Browne, Thomas M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Brownell, Cady (Drawer Medium)
    - Brownell, Frank E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Brownlee, W. C. (William Craig) (Drawer Medium)
    - Browning, Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Brownlow, William G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bruce, George [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Bryan, Goode (Drawer Medium)
    - Bryans, Mortimer, Mrs. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bryant, William Cullen (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Buchanan, James (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Buchanan, Stewart (family group) (Drawer Medium)
    - Buckingham, C. P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Buckingham, William W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Buckland, Ralph P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Buckley, Charles W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Buckley, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Buckmaster, John Williams CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Buell, Alex H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Buell, Don Carlos (Drawer Medium)
    - Buell, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Buford, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Buller, Redvers (Drawer Medium)
    - Bülow, Hans Von (Drawer Medium)
    - Bunting, Thomas C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Burbank, Sidney (Drawer Medium)
    - Burbeck, Henry (Drawer Medium)
    - Burdett, John Lathrop (Drawer Medium)
    - Burgis, Tristam (Drawer Medium)
    - Burgoyne, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Burke, James "Deaf" (Drawer Medium)
    - Burke, Edmund (Drawer Medium)
    - Burling, George C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Burlingame, Anson (Drawer Medium)
    - Burnett, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Burney, Frances (Drawer Medium)
    - Burns, Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - Burns, Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Burnside, Ambrose (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Burr, Aaron (Drawer Medium)
    - Burroughs, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Burt, W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Burton, Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Bush, George Herbert Walker (Drawer Medium)
    - Bush, Irving T. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bushnell, Charles I. (Drawer Medium)
    - Bussey, Cyrus (Drawer Medium)
    - Bussey, Hester Kingsland (Drawer Medium)
    - Bussing, John Schermerhorn (Drawer Medium)
    - Butler, A. P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Butler, Benjamin (Drawer Medium)
    - Butler, William Allen, and wife (Drawer Medium)
    - Butler, William O. (Drawer Medium)
    - Byrne, John J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Byron, George Gordon, Lord (Drawer Medium)
    - Cadwalader (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Cadwalader, Frances
      Cadwalader, George
      Cadwalader, John
      Cadwalader, Thomas
    - Cadwell. P. A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cady, Harriette (Drawer Medium)
    - Caldwell, D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Caldwell, George Alfred (Drawer Medium)
    - Caldwell, J. G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Caldwell, William Mackay (Drawer Medium)
    - Calhoun, John C. (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Callahan, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Cameron, James D. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Cameron, Simon (Drawer Medium)
    - Campbell, Alex W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Campbell, Duncan Pearsall (Drawer Medium)
    - Campbell, Hugh (Drawer Medium)
    - Campbell, J. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Campbell, John A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Campbell, John, Lord (Drawer Medium)
    - Campbell, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Candy, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Cannon, James Spencer (Drawer Medium)
    - Cannon, Joseph Gurney (Drawer Medium)
    - Canoune, Howard M., Mrs. (Drawer Medium)
    - Canoune, Howard Legrand (Drawer Medium)
    - Canova, Antonio (Drawer Medium)
    - Capehart, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Capers, Ellison (Drawer Medium)
    - Capps, Edna Ward (Drawer Medium)
    - Carden, Robert Walter (Drawer Medium)
    - Cardozo, Benjamin N. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cardross, David (Drawer Medium)
    - Carey, E. L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Carey, Eleanor (Drawer Medium)
    - Carey, Silas (Drawer Medium)
    - Carleton, William T. (Drawer Medium)
    - Carlin, William P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Carlyle, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Carnegie, Louise Whitfield (Drawer Medium)
    - Carnochan, J. M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Carolus-Duran, Charles Emile Auguste (Drawer Medium)
    - Carpenter, Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Carr, E. A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Carr, Joseph B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Carrier-Belleuse, Louis-Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Carroll, Anna Ella (Drawer Medium)
    - Carroll, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Carroll, John (Rev.) [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Carroll, S. S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Carson, Kit (Drawer Medium)